Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Fortunoff Video Archive for Holocaust Testimonies records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1944–2017; Accession 2018-A-0014
  - Researcher forms and cataloging work forms
    - Cataloging work records
      - HVT 2151-2200, 1991 February–1997 February (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - HVT 2201-2250, 1991 March–1993 January (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - HVT 2251-2300, 1990 April–1994 January (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - HVT 2301-2350, 1988 May–1994 May (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - HVT 2351-2400, 1990 July–1994 April (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - HVT 2401-2450, 1991 October–1994 May (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - HVT 2451-2500, 1991 February–1994 June (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - HVT 2501-2550, 1992 June–1994 February (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - HVT 2551-2600, 1991 May–1994 July (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - HVT 2601-2650, 1991 February–1994 August (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - HVT 2651- 2700, 1992 June–1997 November (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - HVT 2701- 2750, 1990 August–1995 January (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - HVT 2751- 2800, 1991 July–1995 June (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - HVT 2801- 2850, 1991 July–1995 May (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - HVT 2851-2900, 1990 September–1995 May (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - HVT 2901-2950, 1993 November–1994 June (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - HVT 2951-3000, 1992 March–1995 March (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - HVT 3001-3050, 1983 March–1990 December (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - HVT 3051- 3100, 1983 November–1990 December (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - HVT 3101- 3150, 1983 April–1995 October (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - HVT 3151-3200, 1990 December–1997 March (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - HVT 3201-3250, 1990 June–1995 July (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - HVT 3251-3300, 1984 September–1996 June (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - HVT 3301-3350, 1991 May–1996 January (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - HVT 3351-3400, 1992 January–2000 January (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - HVT 3401-3450, 1990 December–1996 May (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - HVT 3451- 3500, 1992 August–1996 October (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - HVT 3501-3550, 1992 February–1996 May (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - HVT 3551-3600, 1993 June–1997 August (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - HVT 3601-3650, 1992 February–1997 June (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - HVT 3651-3700, 1993 November–1995 December (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - HVT 3701-3750, 1994 May–2001 October (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - HVT 3751-3800, 1994 November–1999 June (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - HVT 3801- 3900, 1993 January–1999 June (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - HVT 3901-4000, 1996 January–2003 May (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - HVT 4001-4100 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - HVT 4101-4200, 1998 February–2001 November (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - HVT 4201-4300, 1998 September–2004 June (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - HVT 4301-4400, 1980 July–2007 July (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - HVT 4401-4500, 1992 February–2017 May (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - HVT 8000-8100, 1980–2006 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Card catalog
      - A-Kh, 1982–1990 (Box 44)
      - Ki-Tr, 1982–1990 (Box 45)
      - Tr-Z, 1982–1990 (Box 46)
  - Berlin Project
    - General, 2005–2011 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Fed-Ex, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Voyager, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Firewriter, Undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Lists -LSF and SML, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence
      - A, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 12-13)
      - B, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 14-15)
      - C, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - D, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - E, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - F, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - G, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - H, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - I, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - J, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - K, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - L, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - M, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - N, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - O, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - P, 2005–2006 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - R, 2005–2006 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - S, 2005–2006 (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
      - T, 2005–2006 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - U, 2005–2006 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - V, 2005–2006 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - W, 2005–2006 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Z, 2005–2006 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Computer files [born digital]
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
    - 25th anniversary photos Fortunoff Video Archive, 2018-A-0014-0001; 1 (Box 48)
    - Disc 1 images 1-23, 2018-A-0014-0002; 1 (Box 48)
    - Disc 3 images 24-50, 2018-A-0014-0003; 1 (Box 48)
    - Disc 3 images 51-59, 2018-A-0014-0004; 1 (Box 48)
    - M. Felsteiner mf@sfsu.edu (650) 322-7727, 2018-A-0014-0005; 1 (Box 48)
    - SAMMA photos, 2018-A-0014-0006; 1 (Box 48)
    - Abraham W., 2018-A-0014-0007; 1 (Box 48)
    - Maurice Hatton Mithras Films, 2018-A-0014-0008; 1 (Box 48)
    - Newsletter Spring 2003 images, 2018-A-0014-0009; 1 (Box 48)
    - Video archive newsletter and graphics, 2018-A-0014-0010; 1 (Box 48)
    - Millenium GWBasic Type "Zion", 2018-A-0014-0011; 1 (Box 48)
    - Fortunoff 25th anniversary poster, 2018-A-0014-0012; 1 (Box 48)
    - Slifka Center Exhibit-labels for Video Archive, 2018-A-0014-0013; 1 (Box 48)
    - H. Greenspan Conf. paper "Memory and Justice", 2018-A-0014-0014; 1 (Box 48)
    - Yale "Reflections on Child Victims and Education", 2018-A-0014-0015; 1 (Box 48)
    - Testimony Pamphlet, 2018-A-0014-0016; 1 (Box 48)
    - HVT Video Archive 89-90 Annual report first draft, 2018-A-0014-0017; 1 (Box 48)